{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "74 + 6",
      "answer": 80
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 1",
      "answer": 34
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 57",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 42",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 61",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 52",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 72",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 29",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 57",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 44",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 29",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 59",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 28",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 22",
      "answer": 37
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 39",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 99",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 60",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 52",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 97",
      "answer": 196
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 85",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 52",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 42",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 44",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 33",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 45",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 72",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 86",
      "answer": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 50",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 9",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 80",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 30",
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 2",
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 53",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 90",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 85",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 11",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 80",
      "answer": 177
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 22,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 37,
    "range": {
      "from": 2100,
      "to": 2137
    }
  }
}